AS YOU STOOD BY
EUN-SU
You have gone off route.
Can you gift wrap this for me?
I'll take it.
Sure.
Hey, Hui-su.
Are you at the restaurant already?
No, I can't make it.
I'm still at home, Eun-su.
Why? Are you under the weather?
My publisher wanted to meet last minute.
Dear valued customers.
Thank you
for visiting Lavie Department Store.
You said you're still at home though.
I am. I'll call you tomorrow.
...popular brands
at the kitchenware department
on the 8th floor.
Yeah.
That's a great idea for the display.
- You like it?
- Mm-hmm, do that.
Your attention, please.
My expectations are very high
for the watch department.
We've given this sales opportunity
to our best team members this year.
Good luck, all.
You got this.
- Yeah, I really like the new line.
- How about this?
An ornate design would look lovely on you.
How about this one?
- We'll think about it.
- Very well.
Thank you.
Do our shops here compare?
They do,
but I haven't been back to China in ages.
Sorry, I could tell you're Chinese.
I hope you enjoy living here.
Really nice to meet you.
Would you like to try it on?
I haven't told you which one I like yet.
This one's part of our premium collection,
set with 90 diamonds.
It's one of the thinnest
automatic watches ever made.
That was perfectly described.
Shame it looks so good on me.
Does it look good?
Well,
I've got better.
I think this collection
will suit you perfectly fine, sir.
Please, take a look.
It doesn't have diamonds.
True, but if you ask me,
the carefully crafted steel case
and band is elegant in and of itself.
No need for gold, platinum, or diamonds.
Hmm.
A man's gotta have diamonds though.
Yes, of course.
Huh? What's going on?
What's wrong?
One's missing.
Which one?
The one that's supposed
to be in this spot, it's gone.
What's going on?
It's from the premium limited collection.
The one with diamonds on the bezel.
Uh... Oh...
Ms. Jo, what should we do?
Oh no! What do we do?
Just wait a minute.
I'm the only one
who handled that watch today.
You two did nothing wrong.
This is my fault.
Right there.
- Can you zoom in on him?
- Sure.
Hey, he looked
straight at the security camera.
Should we file a police report?
I don't know.
We'll have to inform
the director if we do.
I think I'd rather Ms. Jo
check our invitation list first.
He came as a special guest
of Chairman Ma of Shanghai.
His name won't be on the list.
I think you should try it on.
- Glad to see you, Mr. Chairman.
- Hi, nice to see you.
Chairman.
I think I can find the guy.
Thank you.
JIN SO-BAEK
Hello, miss?
Oh my God!
- How many trucks are coming in?
- Two more in the afternoon.
Yeah, I got it right here.
We still have it in stock, no problem.
How many would you like? Three?
I haven't reported it
to the director yet,
so we're not in a position
to go to the police at this point.
For now, just find him
and tell him that we're onto him.
We know he stole the watch.
Excuse me, sir, there's a mistake with
the order we're shipping to Lao Gan Ma.
It's supposed to be ten,
but here it says thirty-five.
Um...
Just do 15. That's what it should've said.
Fifteen? Perfect.
I'll change the order.
Hello again.
You got here bright and early.
I bet you haven't had breakfast yet.
I know a great haejang-guk place.
I'll treat you.
How about I take the watch,
and the food's on me?
I don't have time to go out to eat,
actually. It's a shame, I'm starving.
Hey, Je-ni!
You gotta check the expiry date!
Please, Mr. Chen Shaobo,
could you show me
the watch you took yesterday?
What watch?
We're in Korea.
Jin So-baek is what I go by here,
or Mr. Jin, whatever you prefer, okay?
I'm busy, so hurry up.
Anyway, I don't have the watch on me.
- If you left it at home--
- I actually gave it to someone.
I already sent it out.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
I didn't sell it or anything.
I'll be sure to pay for it right away
if the guy likes it.
- And what if this person doesn't like it?
- No big deal. I'll return it.
Simple.
I'm aware that you were
invited by Chairman Ma.
You're also an acquaintance
of Chairman Wang.
In light of that,
we've decided to give you a day's time.
But we insist you make your purchase
today, before the store closes.
All right, sounds good.
I'll know later on.
I know it's a lot of work for you. Right?
If I end up buying it,
I'll put in a good word at the store.
My name is Jo Eun-su.
Right. I'll mention Jo Eun-su,
assistant manager.
I really think we should put
what you just said in writing.
It's not like it would be
binding or anything.
If you're worried about it,
report me to the police. I don't care.
See you tomorrow.
Have a good evening, everyone!
Have a good one!
There's construction out front.
Gee.
Do you know how many exits there are here?
There's one there.
Figures.
First thing you check
when you're out collecting
is where all the exits are.
You've gotta learn that.
It's basic.
Well, I do know how to persist.
This day is far from over,
so please sign our agreement.
I've always found it way more effective
to carry a knife than a pen though.
Right.
But I don't have a knife.
Enjoy.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
Jingang Chinese Market,
second floor.
Take it. Go ahead.
HUI-SU
SORRY, I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
Thieving punk knew it was a bribe,
but he kept insisting it was a gift.
Go figure.
You afraid that one's a knockoff?
I doubt you would do such a thing,
but I'm not so sure about the punk.
It's the right watch.
The only issue is the strap
has a small mark.
Are you serious? I checked it thoroughly.
It's fine, you can just buff it out.
Our establishment would never sell
a watch with a buffed-out strap.
I'm sorry, but we're going to need you
to purchase this, Mr. Jin.
The day's not over yet.
We're open to you buying
just the strap though.
I think it may please you to know
that only 100 of these straps
crafted with high-end alligator leather
are made each year.
It's pricey, but it will look lovely
with the watch you've got on.
I can put it on now.
Thanks, but I don't need it.
I'm willing to pay you three million won.
You know it's a great offer.
Sorry, that won't work.
You've got a lot to learn
about winning people over.
You should've come back at five million.
You should've thought
about not stealing it.
I mean, inadvertently take it.
You don't have to do this.
You won't get a raise, will you?
Actually, I have sights
on becoming an executive.
I've never made a bad deal.
I'm not in the habit of losing.
JINGANG CHINESE MARKET
Why'd you steal the watch anyway?
I already explained to you.
I just borrowed it for a while.
You know, I didn't realize it when
I looked at this place from the outside,
but this isn't just
an average retail shop.
You run this market a lot more
like a major trading company.
I wasn't sure the deal would go through.
You can't expect me to buy the watch
just to return it later.
Oh.
You just spouted out
such complete nonsense,
and you were so confident,
I almost bought it.
Jo Eun-su.
I want you to tell me something.
Do you ever...
let your wild bitch come out?
I'm pretty sure you do everything
you can to keep it under control.
How would you like to come
work for me, Eun-su?
Oof. Uh, no.
Just hand over your watch
to let me change the strap, okay?
Do you hear this clattering?
It's supposed to help you relax
when you're stressed out.
Well, I just got ripped off,
so I need a whole lot of clattering.
Clatter, clatter.
I hope this helps.
Clatter, clatter, clatter.
Clatter, clatter.
I'm pretty clumsy.
You got that right.
Hui-su could do this, no problem.
She's a friend of mine.
She's good with her hands.
She's talented at writing and draws.
She writes kids' books.
Kids' books. Wow!
Yeah, the kind of stories
that end with "happily ever after."
- Oh! The strap--
- Don't worry, next time.
Hold on.
The least I can do is hold this for you.
We had no information on that guy.
None of us knew Jin So-Baek.
The team leader was so worried.
Hey, I knew you'd do it.
You did it on your own.
You did it. You are the best.
Knock it off.
Hey, do me a favor?
Can you bring this to my seat?
Uh, okay.
Hi there!
Oh, hi. Nice to see you.
Likewise. How have you been?
Really well.
Uh...
You think Hui-su will like this?
Sure she will. It's gorgeous.
What's the occasion though?
It's not her birthday or your anniversary.
Well, I love surprising her.
He spoils her.
He's one of our regular customers.
It's weird.
Hui-su doesn't come by here often.
I always shop alone.
She loves getting my surprises.
She does?
That's strange. She reads the end of
mystery novels before starting them.
It's all wrapped up, sir.
Wonderful, thanks so much. See you soon.
After you.
Take care. Nice seeing you.
He's really mellowed out.
HUI-SU
MRS. KANG HUI-YEON
Yes, ma'am?
Oh, Mrs. Kang.
Are you all right?
Zip me up, will you?
Sure.
Eun-su, I thought...
you would be different.
It's all right.
You know, our VIP sales team
truly values our clients'... privacy--
Sir.
Here you are.
You'd look much better...
with a jacket on.
Lovely.
You can wear it home.
Of course. Go right ahead, Mrs. Kang.
How do you like the outfit, Ms. Jo?
It suits her well.
You have a good eye for fashion.
Come to think of it,
there's a great pair of shoes
that'll perfectly complete this look
at the boutique next door.
May I escort her there?
You already know my wife's size.
Have them delivered.
Yes, I will.
We have tons of great shoes here.
Wouldn't those work?
Sure, why not?
We could've made
a lot more sales during those 50 minutes.
Why did Mrs. Kang need so much attention?
It's fine, I won't tell.
Did something happen
with Mr. Kwon Seong-cheol?
What's your concern, sir?
Seems he pre-ordered
500 end-of-year gifts in your name.
That's incredible! Well done!
In my name?
I heard you assisted Mrs. Kang today.
I knew Mr. Kwon was a great customer.
He's been one of our top 10 VIPs
for the last ten years or so.
But this is unreal!
Thanks to you,
our team won't have to worry about
our performance this quarter, hmm?
GANGCHEOL JIUJITSU
Tap, tap, tap, tap!
It's pretty useless
to try to buy my silence.
Pretending not to see or hear
is my superpower.
Eun-su.
Not bad for someone
whose mind is elsewhere.
Yeah, but I would've lost a real fight.
MOM'S BIRTHDAY TOMORROW
TELL HER I CAN'T VISIT
CUSTOMER: KANG HUI-YEON
LIVES IN HANNAM-DONG
Eun-su, I thought...
you would be different.
MOM
Hello? Eun-su?
Eun-su, are you there?
What is it, sweetheart?
Hi. Were you sleeping?
No, I haven't gone to bed yet.
Is something wrong?
Your birthday's coming up,
but I can't make it.
I know you're really busy, dear.
It's fine.
You can come some other time.
Yeah, I will. Good night.
Hey, wait, what are you doing up so late?
I'm having some soju.
To relax.
Alone?
Mm-hmm.
Lovely.
What about you?
What are you still doing up at this hour?
At my age,
it's still kind of early in the evening.
I had some beer.
Lovely.
Get some rest.
You know, lately...
I've been enjoying evening strolls
in the park with your father.
So what?
It's nice is all. I'm sure you're tired.
I'll let you go, okay?
I got here too early.
Sweetie.
How'd you find time to come?
I haven't cooked any food.
I came with cake.
Oh, you're here.
All right.
You still keep your knives there?
Don't you find them hard to reach?
Mm.
I don't mind.
I'm used to keeping them there.
Do you always stay at home
during the day?
I spend time with the other ladies
in the neighborhood.
But they always want to go to the sauna.
Yeah, so?
Do you go?
Oh, what's the use?
I can very well relax at home.
I never got why
you were so against going to the sauna.
I feel like I'm the only girl who never
went with her mom when I was little.
I've got an idea.
Why don't we go tomorrow?
Well, your brother called.
He said he was coming over.
Mom, why do you keep tasting that?
Hey, Mom! I'm here.
Dad. Nice to see you.
Look, Ma.
I see.
Oh, you're so strong.
Hard as rock.
Let's have the cake.
Now? Let me clean the table first.
Why bother? Cleaning the table
won't make the cake taste better.
Go on.
We'll light the candles
and get it over with.
It's from a fancy bakery,
so it's really pretty.
Let's take a while to digest our meal.
Then we can light the candles
and take pictures--
You sure do talk a lot.
Dad, please.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Mother ♪
Whoo!
Who cares about some stupid cake?
How dare you talk back to me like that.
I bet you're happy the kids are here
on your birthday after they skipped mine?
- Are you? Are you? Dammit!
- No, Mom!
You still beat her, Dad?
It's fine, Eun-su.
It's not what it looks like.
I just got up to go to the bathroom,
and then I...
Is that why you still keep
the kitchen knives under the counter?
So he can't throw them at you?
How dare you!
You really told her about that?
Do you even know Mom tried to kill herself
when I was in high school?
Sweetheart...
What?
It still haunts me to this day!
It drives me crazy!
No, Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom, no!
Mommy, don't do it!
Oh, darling.
Did he hit you again?
He didn't. He didn't touch me.
He doesn't beat me.
He still does, all the time, Ma!
You can't tell your brother
or your father.
Ma.
Gyeong-gu wouldn't let me go to bed.
We gamed all night.
- Eun-su, you leaving already?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna wash up and head out too.
Let's go together.
No, I'm taking Dad to work.
We're going now.
Hey.
About last night...
No. City Hall is that way.
Eun-su.
Get out of the car and go turn yourself in
for domestic violence.
I won't let you hurt her ever again.
Don't get cheeky with me.
Turn the car around.
I never laid a finger on you two kids.
I feel awful. I was a coward about it.
You should've just hit me too!
At least then, I wouldn't have been
pretending I didn't know
what was going on.
I'll go report you myself!
I dare you to try!
You think they'll give a damn?
It's a domestic matter.
Get out of the car.
What are you doing?
How dare you!
GANGNEUNG POLICE STATION
Hey!
Cut it out!
What's the matter?
Hey, Eun-su.
Stop it, okay?
Who do you think you are?
We didn't do anything wrong.
It's fine.
We'll stop.
What's going on?
Since when are they close?
Why's she freaking out like that?
Hui-su.
Hey, Hui-su.
I'm right outside your house.
You're not answering.
I was just at my folks' place.
I thought about you and wanted to see ya.
Uh...
Stand clear of the closing doors.
Hui-su!
Hey, it's me! What's going on?
You're avoiding me, right?
What's going on?
I know something's wrong. Let me in.
It's not a good time.
I'll call you later.
Dammit!
Come on!
Why won't you tap out?
Does this concern you?
A FEW HOURS EARLIER
Uh, it concerns a friend.
All right, you wanna file a report?
What?
Are you here to file a report?
- Hey, Officer Kim.
- Yes, sir.
You've reached
Sinsa Police Station. How may I help you?
Feels like I'm at a restaurant,
and you're asking me what I want to order.
Tap!
Tap, tap, tap, tap! Hey, tap!
You didn't hear him tap out?
We could hear him across the room.
Eun-su.
No sparring for a month.
You're banned from the gym for 30 days.
- Let's play hide-and-seek.
- All right, who's it?
Sh!
Eun-su, I'm getting sleepy.
Let's play a little longer. Hmm?
Eun-su! Get out!
You're gonna drown!
I've got you!
Peace!
Peace.
- We got this!
- Great girls!
- Do a heart shape.
- One more smile. One, two, three.
- Cheese.
- Eun-su. Get in here!
All right.
What are you doing? I look great.
I called to ask
when you'd replace my watch strap.
The bar owner asked me to come get you.
I'm sorry.
Thanks, I'll pay you back.
I always pay my debts.
You should.
Did someone beat you?
I heard you talking in your sleep
on the ride here.
Uh...
What would you do, Mr. Jin,
if you found out someone you love
was getting beaten?
Anyway, thanks a lot for yesterday.
I've gotta run. I'm sorry.
Uh, sorry.
Oh.
JINGANG CHINESE MARKET
EUN-HYEOK
Eun-su.
I'm going back home.
I applied for a transfer.
Yeah, why?
Gyeong-gu's younger brother
is a police officer.
Said he saw you and Dad at the station.
When we were kids,
we used to hide in the closet a lot.
It wasn't to play hide-and-seek, was it?
Why would we both hide if it was just
the two of us playing? Doesn't make sense.
- That means Dad was it, right?
You were just a kid too back then.
Eun-su, sorry.
You didn't know.
You were small.
You did good.
You told on Dad.
Don't worry. I'm gonna take care of Mom.
Get back to work. Make some money.
HUI-SU, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
HAVE YOU HAD LUNCH?
THE WEATHER'S LOVELY, LOOK OUTSIDE
Done, sir.
So I've got your receipt
and the warranty card for the watch strap.
And this is what I owe you
for the bar tab.
Thanks again.
You can treat me
to a meal, okay?
To thank me for giving back the watch.
It's crucial in life to let go of
the insignificant things to move forward.
What if they aren't insignificant?
Then unleash that crazy bitch in you.
We have
an unfortunate incident to report.
There was a tragic accident
involving a woman who ended her life
by throwing herself in front of
the car her husband was driving.
The tragedy took place
in an upscale residential area in Seoul.
Kang, the woman, was struck and killed by
a large SUV driven by Kwon, her husband,
a successful corporate executive.
The husband's lawyer insists
it was just an accident.
However, information has been leaked
that the victim's body
shows evidence of repeated physical abuse.
Ms. Jo? Have you heard the news?
Mrs. Kang has died!
Huh?
We have to pick out black mourning attire
for the bereaved family
and go to the funeral home.
Ms. Jo?
Are you there? Ms. Jo?
Eun-su, I thought
you would be different.
MOM
Hey, Eun-su.
Why are you answering Mom's phone?
She's just washing her hair.
Hmm.
Okay, I'll call later.
HUI-SU
I have to go.
I gotta face this.
You're not gonna say something dumb like,
"I could've saved her," are you?
How are you gonna drive?
You're shaking like a leaf.
I have to check on her.
She should have actually
killed her husband.
Why should she have suffered and died?
She should have gotten revenge.
These abusive assholes.
What the hell?
I'm fine.
We'll have lunch this week. You should go.
Hui-su.
Oh my God! Get down from there!
- Eun-su!
- I'm here.
- I can't take another day of this.
- Don't you dare!
Don't give up, please!
I don't wanna die by his hand.
I have to end it myself.
You're not gonna die.
If anyone's gonna die, it's Jin-pyo.